claimid.com 2013-01-15

# claimID.com/privacy - Manage your online identity

## This Privacy Policy may change from time to time without notice.

  1. **Introduction**

ClaimID.com respects each individual's right to personal privacy. We will collect and use information through our Web site only in the ways disclosed in this statement. This statement applies solely to information collected at claimID.com's Web site.

  2. **Information Collection**

ClaimID.com collects information through our Web site in order to provide users an efficient experience. We collect the personal information, including email addresses, of registered users. We also collect the IP address and use activity of visitors to our website, in order to diagnose and debug our systems and services. We may also collect ancillary usage information, including referrals, access times and platform type, which our users divulge through visiting the site.

ClaimID.com employs cookies. A cookie is a small text file that our Web server places on a user's computer hard drive to be a unique identifier. Cookies enable claimID.com to track usage patterns and deliver customized content to users. Our cookies have an expiration date, and do not collect personally identifiable information.

ClaimID.com uses Google Analytics and Sitemeter for statistics tracking. For more information, please review the [Google Analytics Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy.html), and the [Sitemeter Privacy Statement](http://sitemeter.com/?a=privacy). 

ClaimID.com does not actively market to children, and we never knowingly ask a child under 13 to divulge personal information.

  3. **Information Usage**

We will not rent or sell your personal information to third parties. We will share personal information only in the following cases: 1) Business Transfer: If claimID.com were acquired, personal information would be transferred forward in accordance with acquisition agreements. 2) Legal Compliance: If compelled by law to share information, claimID.com would be required to do so.

The information collected by claimID.com will be used for in-house service analysis and academic research. Basically, this means that we will study anonymized samples of information from claimID.com. The important thing for you to know is the data we study will not identify you personally. We (the people who run claimID.com) are information science graduate students, so we may also use this anonymized, non-personally identifiable data for collaborative academic research. We are bound by very strict institutional guidelines when we use claimID.com data for research, so please know that maintaining your privacy is our utmost concern.

Unless they opt in, claimID.com users will not receive announcements from us. We may provide users the ability to opt-in to communications from claimID.com, but we will never contact you unless you opt-in to these communications.

  4. **Information Storage and Control**

When a user deletes their account from claimID.com, all of their information is expunged from our systems. Of course, our backups may contain older copies of the information, but we expunge backups regularly. We believe that you control your information, and we absolutely respect that.

  5. **Your Identity Rights**

ClaimID.com believes that you control your identity information. While our service (the website, its code, our proprietary goods) are copyright, the identity information that you enter into ClaimID.com isn't. We place a **Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 2.0** license on your information. You may read this license [here](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/2.0/). This means that you may do what you want with your identity information. You may remix, retransmit and copy your identity information, among other things as stipulated by the license. At claimID.com we strongly support identity rights and the Creative Commons, and we strongly support your right to use your personal information as you see fit.

  6. **Problem Resolution**

If problems arise, users may contact claimID.com by emailing [support@claimid.com](mailto:support@claimid.com).
